<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://gamesyall.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://gamesyall.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-09-18T11:14:50-05:00</updated><id>https://gamesyall.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Games Y’all</title><subtitle>*Games Y'all* is a meetup presented by the Museum of Human Achievement,  held every month at venues around Austin for indie devs, digital artists,  and games fans. Games Y'all celebrates, amplifies, and supports the  unique and underrepresented within indie games and beyond.  Come play games, share what you're working on, hang out and meet friends.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Juegos Rancheros presents: NYU No Quarter</title><link href="https://gamesyall.com/events/2019/03/04/juegos-rancheros-presents-nyu-no-quarter.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Juegos Rancheros presents: NYU No Quarter" /><published>2019-03-04T14:39:16-06:00</published><updated>2019-03-04T14:39:16-06:00</updated><id>https://gamesyall.com/events/2019/03/04/juegos-rancheros-presents-nyu-no-quarter</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://gamesyall.com/events/2019/03/04/juegos-rancheros-presents-nyu-no-quarter.html"><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>JUEGOS RANCHEROS is excited to share <a href="https://gamecenter.nyu.edu/">NYU Game Center</a>'s 2018 games from <a href="https://gamecenter.nyu.edu/events/no-quarter/no-quarter-2018/"><strong>No Quarter</strong></a>. Join us WEDNESDAY, March 6th at 7:00 PM at Austin's North Door for a selection of commissioned games by NYU.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2276171855930605/">[RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK HERE]</a></p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2277" src="/images/jr-archive/Neves_NoQuarter2018_corrected_26Nov2018_final2-683x1024.png" alt=""   /></p>
<p>The selected artists include - Brianna Lei, Ivan Safrin, Ethan Redd, and Ayla Myers.</p>
<p>You can read more about NYU's No Quarter Exhibition here:<br />
<a href="https://gamecenter.nyu.edu/events/no-quarter/no-quarter-2018/">https://gamecenter.nyu.edu/events/no-quarter/no-quarter-2018/</a></p>
<p>In addition to our favorites, we’ll also be showcasing more multi- and single-player games by the game’s developers, on top of the usual ‘indie alley’ games brought in by Austin’s local game community!</p>
<p>You can play these games and more Wednesday, March 6th, at 7:00PM at North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702, with a short introduction at 8:00PM. The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!</p>]]></content><author><name>{&quot;login&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;&quot;juegosrancheros@gmail.com&quot;, &quot;display_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;first_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS&quot;, &quot;last_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;RANCHEROS&quot;}</name><email>juegosrancheros@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Events" /><category term="juegosrancheros" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[&nbsp; JUEGOS RANCHEROS is excited to share NYU Game Center's 2018 games from No Quarter. Join us WEDNESDAY, March 6th at 7:00 PM at Austin's North Door for a selection of commissioned games by NYU. [RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK HERE] The selected artists include - Brianna Lei, Ivan Safrin, Ethan Redd, and Ayla Myers. You can read more about NYU's No Quarter Exhibition here: https://gamecenter.nyu.edu/events/no-quarter/no-quarter-2018/ In addition to our favorites, we’ll also be showcasing more multi- and single-player games by the game’s developers, on top of the usual ‘indie alley’ games brought in by Austin’s local game community! You can play these games and more Wednesday, March 6th, at 7:00PM at North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702, with a short introduction at 8:00PM. The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Juegos Rancheros Presents: After Dark</title><link href="https://gamesyall.com/events/2019/02/04/juegos-rancheros-presents-after-dark.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Juegos Rancheros Presents: After Dark" /><published>2019-02-04T15:31:44-06:00</published><updated>2019-02-04T15:31:44-06:00</updated><id>https://gamesyall.com/events/2019/02/04/juegos-rancheros-presents-after-dark</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://gamesyall.com/events/2019/02/04/juegos-rancheros-presents-after-dark.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2266" src="/images/jr-archive/Juegos_Rancheros_Feb_2019.png" alt=""   /></p>
<p>Juegos Rancheros is excited to present a special event for the month of February— <strong>After Dark</strong>, a showcase of 18+, adult-only games focused on sexuality. Join us WEDNESDAY February 6th at 7:00 PM at Austin’s North Door for a night of enjoying adult-themed video games!</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/533658940475654/">[RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK HERE]</a></strong></p>
<h2><a href="http://juegosrancheros.com/safe-spaces/">Safe Spaces Policy</a></h2>
<p>In advance of this event, we want to be sure to put a spotlight on our <strong><a href="http://juegosrancheros.com/safe-spaces/">Safe Spaces Policy.</a></strong><br />
While the games being shown at this evening's event contain content that is of a sexual nature, that does not translate to an invitation for interactions of a sexual nature or any behavior that is harassing or made to make anyone feel uncomfortable. We encourage everyone to review our Safe Spaces Policy, and leave an open invitation for everyone to <a href="http://juegosrancheros.com/board/">reach out to a board member</a> if you have any questions, comments, or concerns about our policy.</p>
<h2><a href="https://freelives.net/games/genital-jousting/">Genital Jousting</a></h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2267" src="/images/jr-archive/KEsbq4.png" alt=""   /></p>
<p><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/469820/Genital_Jousting/">Genital Jousting</a> is an online and local multiplayer party game about flaccid penises and wiggly anuses for up to eight players at once. Players control a detached penis complete with testicles and an anus. Multiple game modes provide a stimulating orgy of objectives: penetrate and be penetrated as fast as possible or compete in absurd, silly and sexually suggestive games and challenges.</p>
<p>In Story Mode, play as John, a dick who wants to find a date for his high school reunion. He'll need some help along the way. He's wobbly, he's soft. But he wants to be hard. So very hard. He wants to show everyone his astounding rigidity. And with your help, that's exactly what he'll do.</p>
<p>Genital Jousting was developed by <a href="https://freelives.net/">Free Lives</a>(<a href="https://twitter.com/Free_Lives">@Free_Lives</a>) and published by <a>Devolver Digital (</a><a href="https://twitter.com/DevolverDigital">@DevolverDigital</a><a>). </a></p>
<h2><a href="https://radiator.debacle.us/">Radiator 2: Anniversary Edition</a></h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2268" src="/images/jr-archive/zlSyPw.jpg" alt=""   /></p>
<p><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/385370/Radiator_2_Anniversary_Edition/">Radiator 2: Anniversary Edition</a> is a small threesome of experimental games about male sexuality (Hurt Me Plenty, Succulent, and Stick Shift) about punishing, eating, and driving.</p>
<p>These small short games attempt to expand eroticism in games beyond a cutscene and fade-to-black. What if sex in games was something we performed as players, instead of something we obtained? What might sex mechanics look like? How can we convey intimacy in games? That's what Radiator 2 tries to explore.</p>
<p>The collection was developed by <a href="https://debacle.us/">Robert Yang</a> (<a href="https://twitter.com/radiatoryang">@radiatoryang</a>).</p>
<h2><a href="http://luxuria-superbia.com/">Luxuria Superbia</a></h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2269" src="/images/jr-archive/a6ca10a3c457550a2f29be07278cd4fc8b25c1b1.jpg" alt=""   /></p>
<p>A simple game of touch, pleasure and joy made for fingers on touchscreens and joysticks on computers.</p>
<p><a href="https://taleoftales.itch.io/luxuria-superbia">Luxuria Superbia</a> is a musical journey from the sensuous to the spiritual. Exciting designs explode from your gestures as you glide through tunnels, beautiful as flowers. It's all about the experience and the interaction.</p>
<p>Positive, optimistic, joyous, encouraging and perhaps even instructional.<br />
Designed by Michaël Samyn and Auriea Harvey with music by Walter Hus.</p>
<h2><a href="http://ladykillerinabind.com/">Ladykiller in a Bind</a></h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2270" src="/images/jr-archive/capsule_main.png" alt=""   /></p>
<p><em>My Twin Brother Made Me Crossdress As Him And Now I Have To Deal With A Geeky Stalker And A Domme Beauty Who Want Me In A Bind!! or, Ladykiller in a Bind</em></p>
<p><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/560000/Ladykiller_in_a_Bind/"> Ladykiller in a Bind</a> is an erotic romantic comedy about social manipulation, crossdressing, and girls tying up other girls. Will the hapless lesbian ladykiller Beast succeed at pretending to be her ruthless twin? By the creators of Analogue: A Hate Story, featuring choice-driven mechanics... and lots of sex.</p>
<p>Forced to pretend to be her twin brother on a cruise ship full of his classmates and enemies, the Beast finds herself thrown into a game of complex social manipulation, as well as literal bondage. Can you win enough of their votes to get back the Beast's motorcycle? Will you get locked up in cargo for doing too unconvincing an impression of the Beast's brother? Or will you just spend the whole time brazenly <strong>[CENSORED]</strong>?</p>
<p>Ladykiller was developed by Christine Love (<a href="https://twitter.com/christinelove">@christinelove</a>) / <a href="http://loveconquersallgam.es/">Love Conquers All Games</a>.</p>
<p>You can play these games and more Wednesday, February 6th, at 7:00PM at North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702, with a short introduction at 8:00PM. The 18+ show is free and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!</p>]]></content><author><name>{&quot;login&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;&quot;juegosrancheros@gmail.com&quot;, &quot;display_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;first_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS&quot;, &quot;last_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;RANCHEROS&quot;}</name><email>juegosrancheros@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Events" /><category term="juegosrancheros" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juegos Rancheros is excited to present a special event for the month of February— After Dark, a showcase of 18+, adult-only games focused on sexuality. Join us WEDNESDAY February 6th at 7:00 PM at Austin’s North Door for a night of enjoying adult-themed video games! [RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK HERE] Safe Spaces Policy In advance of this event, we want to be sure to put a spotlight on our Safe Spaces Policy. While the games being shown at this evening's event contain content that is of a sexual nature, that does not translate to an invitation for interactions of a sexual nature or any behavior that is harassing or made to make anyone feel uncomfortable. We encourage everyone to review our Safe Spaces Policy, and leave an open invitation for everyone to reach out to a board member if you have any questions, comments, or concerns about our policy. Genital Jousting Genital Jousting is an online and local multiplayer party game about flaccid penises and wiggly anuses for up to eight players at once. Players control a detached penis complete with testicles and an anus. Multiple game modes provide a stimulating orgy of objectives: penetrate and be penetrated as fast as possible or compete in absurd, silly and sexually suggestive games and challenges. In Story Mode, play as John, a dick who wants to find a date for his high school reunion. He'll need some help along the way. He's wobbly, he's soft. But he wants to be hard. So very hard. He wants to show everyone his astounding rigidity. And with your help, that's exactly what he'll do. Genital Jousting was developed by Free Lives(@Free_Lives) and published by Devolver Digital (@DevolverDigital). Radiator 2: Anniversary Edition Radiator 2: Anniversary Edition is a small threesome of experimental games about male sexuality (Hurt Me Plenty, Succulent, and Stick Shift) about punishing, eating, and driving. These small short games attempt to expand eroticism in games beyond a cutscene and fade-to-black. What if sex in games was something we performed as players, instead of something we obtained? What might sex mechanics look like? How can we convey intimacy in games? That's what Radiator 2 tries to explore. The collection was developed by Robert Yang (@radiatoryang). Luxuria Superbia A simple game of touch, pleasure and joy made for fingers on touchscreens and joysticks on computers. Luxuria Superbia is a musical journey from the sensuous to the spiritual. Exciting designs explode from your gestures as you glide through tunnels, beautiful as flowers. It's all about the experience and the interaction. Positive, optimistic, joyous, encouraging and perhaps even instructional. Designed by Michaël Samyn and Auriea Harvey with music by Walter Hus. Ladykiller in a Bind My Twin Brother Made Me Crossdress As Him And Now I Have To Deal With A Geeky Stalker And A Domme Beauty Who Want Me In A Bind!! or, Ladykiller in a Bind Ladykiller in a Bind is an erotic romantic comedy about social manipulation, crossdressing, and girls tying up other girls. Will the hapless lesbian ladykiller Beast succeed at pretending to be her ruthless twin? By the creators of Analogue: A Hate Story, featuring choice-driven mechanics... and lots of sex. Forced to pretend to be her twin brother on a cruise ship full of his classmates and enemies, the Beast finds herself thrown into a game of complex social manipulation, as well as literal bondage. Can you win enough of their votes to get back the Beast's motorcycle? Will you get locked up in cargo for doing too unconvincing an impression of the Beast's brother? Or will you just spend the whole time brazenly [CENSORED]? Ladykiller was developed by Christine Love (@christinelove) / Love Conquers All Games. You can play these games and more Wednesday, February 6th, at 7:00PM at North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702, with a short introduction at 8:00PM. The 18+ show is free and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Juegos Rancheros Presents: 2018 // Reflections</title><link href="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/12/27/juegos-rancheros-presents-2018-reflections.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Juegos Rancheros Presents: 2018 // Reflections" /><published>2018-12-27T16:50:47-06:00</published><updated>2018-12-27T16:50:47-06:00</updated><id>https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/12/27/juegos-rancheros-presents-2018-reflections</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/12/27/juegos-rancheros-presents-2018-reflections.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2233" src="/images/jr-archive/JRMonthly_Jan2018_scribbles.png" alt=""   /></p>
<p>JUEGOS RANCHEROS is excited to reflect with you on the new year and share our favorite games from 2018. Join us for a very special catalogue of games chosen by yours truly. Join us <strong>WEDNESDAY</strong> <em>(new year, new weekday!)</em>, <strong>January 2nd at 7:00 PM at Austin's North Door</strong> for a selection of hand picked games from your Juegos Rancheros board members.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/2139062353090729/"><strong>[RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK HERE]</strong></a></p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2232" src="/images/jr-archive/JR_2019_NewNight_Wednesdays.png" alt=""   /></p>
<p>In addition to our favorites, we’ll also be showcasing more multi- and single-player games by the game’s developers, on top of the usual ‘indie alley’ games brought in by Austin’s local game community!</p>
<p>You can play these games and more Wednesday, January 2nd, at 7:00PM at North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702, with a short introduction at 8:00PM. The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!</p>]]></content><author><name>{&quot;login&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;&quot;juegosrancheros@gmail.com&quot;, &quot;display_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;first_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS&quot;, &quot;last_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;RANCHEROS&quot;}</name><email>juegosrancheros@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Events" /><category term="juegosrancheros" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[JUEGOS RANCHEROS is excited to reflect with you on the new year and share our favorite games from 2018. Join us for a very special catalogue of games chosen by yours truly. Join us WEDNESDAY (new year, new weekday!), January 2nd at 7:00 PM at Austin's North Door for a selection of hand picked games from your Juegos Rancheros board members. [RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK HERE] In addition to our favorites, we’ll also be showcasing more multi- and single-player games by the game’s developers, on top of the usual ‘indie alley’ games brought in by Austin’s local game community! You can play these games and more Wednesday, January 2nd, at 7:00PM at North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702, with a short introduction at 8:00PM. The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Juegos Rancheros presents: A VERRY MERRY MULTICART</title><link href="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/12/03/juegos-rancheros-presents-a-verry-merry-multicart.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Juegos Rancheros presents: A VERRY MERRY MULTICART" /><published>2018-12-03T14:21:26-06:00</published><updated>2018-12-03T14:21:26-06:00</updated><id>https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/12/03/juegos-rancheros-presents-a-verry-merry-multicart</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/12/03/juegos-rancheros-presents-a-verry-merry-multicart.html"><![CDATA[<p>JUEGOS RANCHEROS is excited to feature <a href="https://50games.fun/">UFO50</a> and <a href="https://retrogamecrunch.com/">Retro Game Crunch</a> for a very merry selection of multi-cart game collections. Brace the 60 degree Austin winter to join us Thursday, Dec 6th, at 7:00PM at the North Door.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/507683463076172/">[RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK HERE]</a></strong></p>
<h2>UFO 50</h2>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5wqZi1smZOg"  ></iframe></p>
<p><a href="https://50games.fun/">UFO 50</a> is a collection of 50 single and multiplayer games from the creators of Spelunky, Downwell, Time Barons, Skorpulac, and Madhouse. Jump in and explore a variety of genres, from platformers and shoot 'em ups to puzzle games and RPGs. Our goal is to combine a familiar 8-bit aesthetic with new ideas and modern game design sensibilities.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2228" src="/images/jr-archive/UFO50_GIF.gif" alt=""   /></p>
<p>UFO 50 is being published by Mossmouth. The development team behind the project includes: Derek Yu (<a href="https://twitter.com/mossmouth">@mossmouth</a>), Eirik Suhrke (<a href="https://twitter.com/strotchy">@strotchy</a>), Jon Perry (<a href="https://twitter.com/QuibbleGames">@QuibbleGames</a>), Paul Hubans (<a href="https://twitter.com/phubans">@phubans</a>), Ojiro Fumoto (<a href="https://twitter.com/moppin_">@moppin_</a>), and Tyriq Plummer (<a href="https://twitter.com/FourbitFriday">@FourbitFriday</a>).</p>
<h2>Retro Game Crunch</h2>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YGoSLASUJR0"  ></iframe></p>
<p><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/290040/Retro_Game_Crunch/">Retro Game Crunch</a> is a series of 7 games, full of the charm and challenge of the 8-bit generation. Each world feels like an authentic NES classic. This genre-spanning collection includes... Super Clew Land, End of Line, GAIAttack, Paradox Lost, Wub-Wub Wescue, Brains &amp; Hearts, and Shūten!</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2229" src="/images/jr-archive/RetroGameCrunch_GIF1.gif" alt=""   /></p>
<p>Retro Game Crunch is a collaboration between <a href="http://rustymoyher.com/">Rusty Moyher</a>,<a href="https://shauninman.com/pendium/"> Shaun Inman</a>, and <a href="http://8bitmatt.com/">Matt Grimm</a>. In August 2012, the team jammed for 72 hours during Ludum Dare 24 to create the first entry in RGC— Super Clew Land. A <a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/shauninman/retro-game-crunch-six-games-in-six-months">Kickstarter</a>, 6 months, and 6 games later, Retro Game Crunch came to life!</p>
<p>Be sure to join us Thursday, December 6th, at 7:00PM at North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702! Stuff your proverbial stocking with retro games for days.</p>
<p>A short introduction begins at 8:00PM. The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!</p>]]></content><author><name>{&quot;login&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;&quot;juegosrancheros@gmail.com&quot;, &quot;display_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;first_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS&quot;, &quot;last_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;RANCHEROS&quot;}</name><email>juegosrancheros@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Events" /><category term="juegosrancheros" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[JUEGOS RANCHEROS is excited to feature UFO50 and Retro Game Crunch for a very merry selection of multi-cart game collections. Brace the 60 degree Austin winter to join us Thursday, Dec 6th, at 7:00PM at the North Door. [RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK HERE] UFO 50 UFO 50 is a collection of 50 single and multiplayer games from the creators of Spelunky, Downwell, Time Barons, Skorpulac, and Madhouse. Jump in and explore a variety of genres, from platformers and shoot 'em ups to puzzle games and RPGs. Our goal is to combine a familiar 8-bit aesthetic with new ideas and modern game design sensibilities. UFO 50 is being published by Mossmouth. The development team behind the project includes: Derek Yu (@mossmouth), Eirik Suhrke (@strotchy), Jon Perry (@QuibbleGames), Paul Hubans (@phubans), Ojiro Fumoto (@moppin_), and Tyriq Plummer (@FourbitFriday). Retro Game Crunch Retro Game Crunch is a series of 7 games, full of the charm and challenge of the 8-bit generation. Each world feels like an authentic NES classic. This genre-spanning collection includes... Super Clew Land, End of Line, GAIAttack, Paradox Lost, Wub-Wub Wescue, Brains &amp; Hearts, and Shūten! Retro Game Crunch is a collaboration between Rusty Moyher, Shaun Inman, and Matt Grimm. In August 2012, the team jammed for 72 hours during Ludum Dare 24 to create the first entry in RGC— Super Clew Land. A Kickstarter, 6 months, and 6 games later, Retro Game Crunch came to life! Be sure to join us Thursday, December 6th, at 7:00PM at North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702! Stuff your proverbial stocking with retro games for days. A short introduction begins at 8:00PM. The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bring Fantastic Arcade Home With Our Fantastic Six-Game Bundle!</title><link href="https://gamesyall.com/news/2018/10/25/bring-fantastic-arcade-home-with-our-fantastic-six-game-bundle.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bring Fantastic Arcade Home With Our Fantastic Six-Game Bundle!" /><published>2018-10-25T11:37:10-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-25T11:37:10-05:00</updated><id>https://gamesyall.com/news/2018/10/25/bring-fantastic-arcade-home-with-our-fantastic-six-game-bundle</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://gamesyall.com/news/2018/10/25/bring-fantastic-arcade-home-with-our-fantastic-six-game-bundle.html"><![CDATA[<p>Bring <a href="https://fantasticarcade.com/">Fantastic Arcade</a> home to you with six amazing and exclusive games, presented by Austin's independent game collective <a href="http://juegosrancheros.com/">JUEGOS RANCHEROS</a>!</p>
<p><iframe   allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>We brought together six of the most talented indie developers from around the world to create new games, all of which made their debut at our ninth-annual indie game festival, <a href="https://fantasticarcade.com/">Fantastic Arcade</a>, which took place in Austin, TX, October 25th through 28th, 2018.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://juegosrancheros.itch.io/fantastic-arcade-2018">[CLICK HERE OR USE THE WIDGET BELOW TO BUY THE 2018 FANTASTIC ARCADE BUNDLE AND SUPPORT JUEGOS RANCHEROS!]</a></strong></p>
<p><iframe src="https://itch.io/embed/319540"  ></iframe></p>
<p>All proceeds from the sale of this bundle benefit our <a href="http://juegosrancheros.com/about/">non-profit organization</a>. Help us showcase more amazing games both here in Austin and a city near you, and commission more fantastic developers to create new games like these!</p>
<p>Included in this bundle are all six games you see here:</p>
<hr />
<h2><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2209" src="/images/jr-archive/grassstains_banner.png" alt=""   /></h2>
<h2>Grass Stains, by Nina Freeman / Star Maid Games</h2>
<p><em>(2 Controllers recommended to play)</em></p>
<p>Grass Stains is a local multiplayer game about two little kids, their dog, and a soccer ball on a summer day. Kick the ball too hard at your friend and you might just knock them over. Will you play fair and help them up, or tease them while you score point after point? It’s up to you!</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2215" src="/images/jr-archive/grassstains_gif.gif" alt=""   /></p>
<p>Contributors to Grass Stains include <a href="http://ninasays.so/">Nina Freeman</a>, <a href="https://cargocollective.com/aefreedman">Aaron Freedman</a>, <a href="http://radstronomical.com/">Diego Garcia</a>, and <a href="https://www.amosroddy.com/">Amos Roddy</a>. Nina was the designer for <a href="http://ninasays.so/lostmemoriesdotnet/">Lost Memories Dot Net</a>, <a href="http://ninasays.so/cibele/">Cibele</a>, <a href="http://ninasays.so/howdoyoudoit/">how do you Do it?</a> and <a href="http://ninasays.so/kimmy/">Kimmy</a>, as well as part of the <a href="https://fullbrig.ht/">Fullbright</a> team (Tacoma).</p>
<hr />
<h2><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2211" src="/images/jr-archive/ppp_banner.png" alt=""   /></h2>
<h2>Paper Planet Pop, by Tyriq Plummer</h2>
<p>Brave robot Pop is in trouble! Stranded on a strange planet and hunted by the Hand of Hate, he must fend off wave after wave of threats: Coinsteroids, pinvaders, cosmic jellysquid, and space pirates galore! Though Pop is no pushover, the presentiment persists: How long can our plucky protagonist persevere in this petite planetary predicament? Find out in: PAPER PLANET POP!</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2217" src="/images/jr-archive/ppp_gif.gif" alt=""   /></p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/fourbitfriday">Tyriq Plummer</a> is a developer and <a href="http://www.fourbitfriday.com/art.htm">game artist</a> best known for their work on the roguelike platformer <a href="https://www.ckgame.net/">Catacomb Kids</a>. Tyriq also has a reputation as a inventive game jam participant, with numerous <a href="https://ldjam.com/">Ludum Dare</a> titles to their name.</p>
<hr />
<h2><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2212" src="/images/jr-archive/wifirobots_banner.png" alt=""   /></h2>
<h2>WiFi Robots, by George Buckenham</h2>
<p>Did you know: your phone is secretly also a robot? And everyone else in the venue's is, too! Connect them together and hack them all.</p>
<p><a href="http://v21.io/">George Buckenham</a> is a prolific programmer for games (<a href="https://beastsofbalance.com/us/?">Beasts of Balance</a>) and procedurally generated text (<a href="https://cheapbotsdonequick.com/">Cheap Bots, Done Quick!</a>), as well as one of the minds behind rogue party-game revelers <a href="http://thewildrumpus.co.uk/">The Wild Rumpus</a>.</p>
<hr />
<h2><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2207" src="/images/jr-archive/breaker_banner.png" alt=""   /></h2>
<h2>Breaker, by Daniel Linssen</h2>
<p>BREAKER is a weird blend between breakout, space invaders and ikaruga, and features an original, responsive soundtrack by <a href="http://www.dataairlines.net/dubmood/">Dubmood</a> with sound effects by <a href="http://www.martinkvale.com/">Martin Kvale</a>.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2213" src="/images/jr-archive/breaker_gif.gif" alt=""   /></p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/Managore">Daniel Linssen</a> is an Australian developer and artist best known for the games <a href="https://managore.itch.io/roguelight">Roguelight, </a><a href="https://managore.itch.io/windowframe">Windowframe</a> and numerous Ludum Dare jam games. Daniel’s games have consistently inventive play mechanics and lovely, muted color palettes.</p>
<hr />
<h2><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2210" src="/images/jr-archive/kaiju_banner.png" alt=""   /></h2>
<h2>Kaiju Super Datetech, by Powerhoof</h2>
<p>A Giant Monster has appeared in Kyoto II! The city's only hope is for you and your company to construct a Colossal Robot, maneuver your creation to the target creature, and... ask it out to dinner? Or a film? Or something?</p>
<p>Cooperate in building a perfect match for the kaiju, and compete against rival companies to romance the lonely monster in KAIJU SUPER DATETECH!</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2216" src="/images/jr-archive/kaiju_gif.gif" alt=""   /></p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/powerhoof">Powerhoof</a> are Australian indie developers who delighted attendees with their surprise Fantastic Arcade tournament of <a href="http://www.powerhoof.com/regular-human-basketball/">Regular Human Basketball</a>. With their multiplayer dungeon crawler <a href="http://www.powerhoof.com/crawl/">Crawl</a>, they’ve become known for a keen artistic style and multiplayer action.</p>
<hr />
<h2><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2208" src="/images/jr-archive/compettition_banner2.png" alt=""   /></h2>
<h2>ComPETition, by Catt Small</h2>
<p><em>(Controller required to play)</em></p>
<p>ComPETition is a competitive cat petting game for two players. Who will win the cat’s affection before it gets bored? Who will be scratched into shame? Grab a friend and find out in this fuzzball extravaganza!</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2214" src="/images/jr-archive/compettition_gif.gif" alt=""   /></p>
<p><a href="https://cattsmall.com/">Catt Small</a> is an interactive designer and developer who works in user experience and games, as well as organizing and advocating for marginalized groups in tech. Catt previously created the multiplayer game <a href="https://cattsmall.com/portfolio/breakup-squad/">Breakup Squad</a>, as a part of NYU’s 2016 No Quarter Exhibition.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://itch.io/embed/319540"  ></iframe></p>]]></content><author><name>{&quot;login&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;&quot;juegosrancheros@gmail.com&quot;, &quot;display_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;first_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS&quot;, &quot;last_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;RANCHEROS&quot;}</name><email>juegosrancheros@gmail.com</email></author><category term="News" /><category term="juegosrancheros" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bring Fantastic Arcade home to you with six amazing and exclusive games, presented by Austin's independent game collective JUEGOS RANCHEROS! We brought together six of the most talented indie developers from around the world to create new games, all of which made their debut at our ninth-annual indie game festival, Fantastic Arcade, which took place in Austin, TX, October 25th through 28th, 2018. [CLICK HERE OR USE THE WIDGET BELOW TO BUY THE 2018 FANTASTIC ARCADE BUNDLE AND SUPPORT JUEGOS RANCHEROS!] All proceeds from the sale of this bundle benefit our non-profit organization. Help us showcase more amazing games both here in Austin and a city near you, and commission more fantastic developers to create new games like these! Included in this bundle are all six games you see here: Grass Stains, by Nina Freeman / Star Maid Games (2 Controllers recommended to play) Grass Stains is a local multiplayer game about two little kids, their dog, and a soccer ball on a summer day. Kick the ball too hard at your friend and you might just knock them over. Will you play fair and help them up, or tease them while you score point after point? It’s up to you! Contributors to Grass Stains include Nina Freeman, Aaron Freedman, Diego Garcia, and Amos Roddy. Nina was the designer for Lost Memories Dot Net, Cibele, how do you Do it? and Kimmy, as well as part of the Fullbright team (Tacoma). Paper Planet Pop, by Tyriq Plummer Brave robot Pop is in trouble! Stranded on a strange planet and hunted by the Hand of Hate, he must fend off wave after wave of threats: Coinsteroids, pinvaders, cosmic jellysquid, and space pirates galore! Though Pop is no pushover, the presentiment persists: How long can our plucky protagonist persevere in this petite planetary predicament? Find out in: PAPER PLANET POP! Tyriq Plummer is a developer and game artist best known for their work on the roguelike platformer Catacomb Kids. Tyriq also has a reputation as a inventive game jam participant, with numerous Ludum Dare titles to their name. WiFi Robots, by George Buckenham Did you know: your phone is secretly also a robot? And everyone else in the venue's is, too! Connect them together and hack them all. George Buckenham is a prolific programmer for games (Beasts of Balance) and procedurally generated text (Cheap Bots, Done Quick!), as well as one of the minds behind rogue party-game revelers The Wild Rumpus. Breaker, by Daniel Linssen BREAKER is a weird blend between breakout, space invaders and ikaruga, and features an original, responsive soundtrack by Dubmood with sound effects by Martin Kvale. Daniel Linssen is an Australian developer and artist best known for the games Roguelight, Windowframe and numerous Ludum Dare jam games. Daniel’s games have consistently inventive play mechanics and lovely, muted color palettes. Kaiju Super Datetech, by Powerhoof A Giant Monster has appeared in Kyoto II! The city's only hope is for you and your company to construct a Colossal Robot, maneuver your creation to the target creature, and... ask it out to dinner? Or a film? Or something? Cooperate in building a perfect match for the kaiju, and compete against rival companies to romance the lonely monster in KAIJU SUPER DATETECH! Powerhoof are Australian indie developers who delighted attendees with their surprise Fantastic Arcade tournament of Regular Human Basketball. With their multiplayer dungeon crawler Crawl, they’ve become known for a keen artistic style and multiplayer action. ComPETition, by Catt Small (Controller required to play) ComPETition is a competitive cat petting game for two players. Who will win the cat’s affection before it gets bored? Who will be scratched into shame? Grab a friend and find out in this fuzzball extravaganza! Catt Small is an interactive designer and developer who works in user experience and games, as well as organizing and advocating for marginalized groups in tech. Catt previously created the multiplayer game Breakup Squad, as a part of NYU’s 2016 No Quarter Exhibition.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">JUEGOS RANCHEROS Presents: Fantastic Arcade 2018 Preview</title><link href="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/10/01/juegos-rancheros-presents-fantastic-arcade-2018-preview.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="JUEGOS RANCHEROS Presents: Fantastic Arcade 2018 Preview" /><published>2018-10-01T09:26:35-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-01T09:26:35-05:00</updated><id>https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/10/01/juegos-rancheros-presents-fantastic-arcade-2018-preview</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/10/01/juegos-rancheros-presents-fantastic-arcade-2018-preview.html"><![CDATA[<p>Want to get the first look at the amazing games coming to this year's Fantastic Arcade? Then be sure to join us <strong>Thursday, October 4th, at 7:00PM</strong> at Austin's <a href="http://www.ndvenue.com/">North Door</a>, as JUEGOS RANCHEROS presents an international handful of Spotlight and Showcase festival favorites!</p>
<p>[ <a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/1928082654163141/">RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK BY CLICKING HERE!</a> ]</p>
<p>We've announced 30+ games coming to this year's <a href="https://fantasticarcade.com">Fantastic Arcade</a> — and want to give you an early peek at some you still can't play anywhere else!</p>
<p>Games appearing on Thursday will include:</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2196" src="/images/jr-archive/cricket-2.png" alt=""   /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><b><a href="https://fantasticarcade.com//games/2018/cricket-through-the-ages/">Cricket Through the Ages</a> </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Free Lives</span></p>
<p>Over a thousand years ago the human race teetered on the edge of extinction. They were helpless against the mighty behemoths of the land. And then, salvation… Cricket was invented! Go alone, or take a friend of your choice, on a journey through the rich, and exquisitely accurate, history of cricket.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2197" src="/images/jr-archive/levedad-3.png" alt=""   /></p>
<p><b><a href="https://fantasticarcade.com//games/2018/Levedad/">Levedad</a> </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">Solimporta</span></p>
<p>Levedad is a game about capturing time through the contemplative gaze of long exposure photography. It is finding beauty in an ever-changing space where time passes with you and through you.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2198" src="/images/jr-archive/russian_subway_dogs_2018.jpg" alt=""   /></p>
<p><b><a href="https://fantasticarcade.com//games/2018/Russian_Subway_Dogs/">Russian Subway Dogs</a></b> <span style="font-weight: 400;">Spooky Squid Games</span></p>
<p>A fast-paced systemic arcade game inspired by the real-life stray dogs of the Moscow metro. Can you steal enough food to survive? Juggle vodka, cook wildlife, bark fire and more in this surprisingly deep arcade game!</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2199" src="/images/jr-archive/dino_game.png" alt=""   /></p>
<p><b><a href="https://fantasticarcade.com//games/2018/dino_game/">Dino Game</a></b> <span style="font-weight: 400;">Sokpop</span></p>
<p>Dino game is about ladders, systems, and tall things. You fell from your UFO. Learn the rules of a foreign place, and find a way to get back to your space-ship!</p>
<p>You can play all of these games and more <strong>Thursday, October 4th, at 7:00PM <a href="http://www.ndvenue.com/">North Door</a>, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702</strong>, with a short introduction at 8:00PM. The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!</p>]]></content><author><name>{&quot;login&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;&quot;juegosrancheros@gmail.com&quot;, &quot;display_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;first_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS&quot;, &quot;last_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;RANCHEROS&quot;}</name><email>juegosrancheros@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Events" /><category term="juegosrancheros" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get the first look at the amazing games coming to this year's Fantastic Arcade? Then be sure to join us Thursday, October 4th, at 7:00PM at Austin's North Door, as JUEGOS RANCHEROS presents an international handful of Spotlight and Showcase festival favorites! [ RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK BY CLICKING HERE! ] We've announced 30+ games coming to this year's Fantastic Arcade — and want to give you an early peek at some you still can't play anywhere else! Games appearing on Thursday will include: &nbsp; Cricket Through the Ages Free Lives Over a thousand years ago the human race teetered on the edge of extinction. They were helpless against the mighty behemoths of the land. And then, salvation… Cricket was invented! Go alone, or take a friend of your choice, on a journey through the rich, and exquisitely accurate, history of cricket. Levedad Solimporta Levedad is a game about capturing time through the contemplative gaze of long exposure photography. It is finding beauty in an ever-changing space where time passes with you and through you. Russian Subway Dogs Spooky Squid Games A fast-paced systemic arcade game inspired by the real-life stray dogs of the Moscow metro. Can you steal enough food to survive? Juggle vodka, cook wildlife, bark fire and more in this surprisingly deep arcade game! Dino Game Sokpop Dino game is about ladders, systems, and tall things. You fell from your UFO. Learn the rules of a foreign place, and find a way to get back to your space-ship! You can play all of these games and more Thursday, October 4th, at 7:00PM North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702, with a short introduction at 8:00PM. The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fantastic Arcade first wave of titles announced! Tickets on sale Sept 6th!</title><link href="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/09/04/fantastic-arcade-first-wave-of-titles-announced-tickets-on-sale-sept-6th.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fantastic Arcade first wave of titles announced! Tickets on sale Sept 6th!" /><published>2018-09-04T10:00:33-05:00</published><updated>2018-09-04T10:00:33-05:00</updated><id>https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/09/04/fantastic-arcade-first-wave-of-titles-announced-tickets-on-sale-sept-6th</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/09/04/fantastic-arcade-first-wave-of-titles-announced-tickets-on-sale-sept-6th.html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/jr-archive/cricket-1-300x169.png" alt=""   /><br />
JUEGOS RANCHEROS is proud to announce the first wave of attractions for this year’s Fantastic Arcade, hosted by the Alamo Drafthouse Mueller this October 25th-28th (full, four-day passes go on sale SEPT 6th).</p>
<p>Among other exciting news, this year's event will feature new, commissioned works by  <a href="https://twitter.com/hentaiphd">Nina Freeman</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/FourbitFriday">Tyriq Plummer</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/v21">George Buckingham</a>, <a href="https://managore.itch.io/">Daniel Linssen</a>, <a href="http://www.powerhoof.com/">Powerhoof</a>, and <a href="http://cattsmall.com/">Catt Small</a>.</p>
<p>Visit <a href="https://fantasticarcade.com/news/2018/09/04/first_wave_revealed.html">fantasticarcade.com</a> for all the info!</p>]]></content><author><name>{&quot;login&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;&quot;juegosrancheros@gmail.com&quot;, &quot;display_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;first_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS&quot;, &quot;last_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;RANCHEROS&quot;}</name><email>juegosrancheros@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Events" /><category term="juegosrancheros" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[JUEGOS RANCHEROS is proud to announce the first wave of attractions for this year’s Fantastic Arcade, hosted by the Alamo Drafthouse Mueller this October 25th-28th (full, four-day passes go on sale SEPT 6th). Among other exciting news, this year's event will feature new, commissioned works by  Nina Freeman, Tyriq Plummer, George Buckingham, Daniel Linssen, Powerhoof, and Catt Small. Visit fantasticarcade.com for all the info!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">JUEGOS RANCHEROS presents: Deep South Africa</title><link href="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/09/01/juegos-rancheros-presents-deep-south-africa.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="JUEGOS RANCHEROS presents: Deep South Africa" /><published>2018-09-01T12:58:13-05:00</published><updated>2018-09-01T12:58:13-05:00</updated><id>https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/09/01/juegos-rancheros-presents-deep-south-africa</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/09/01/juegos-rancheros-presents-deep-south-africa.html"><![CDATA[<p>JUEGOS RANCHEROS is excited to share DEEP SOUTH AFRICA, a trio of games from developers based in South Africa. Join us this Thursday, Sept 6th, at 7:00PM at Austin’s North Door for a look at Semblance, Helping Hand, and Frog Smashers.<br />
[<a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/534233483701628/">RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK BY CLICKING HERE!</a>]</p>
<p><iframe   allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>Created by duo Nyamakop, Semblance is described as a "true platformer". What does that even mean? Well you can literally manipulate platforms with your body in this soft and squishy world. Come check out one of the first games from South Africa to be released on the Switch.</p>
<p><iframe   allowfullscreen></iframe><br />
Every play a dialogue driven narrative game, but only wanted to respond to every character by giving them the finger? Well in Helping Hand you can! Along with a variety of different hand gestures you can navigate this Adult Swim show-esque game with just the use of 5 fingers.</p>
<p><iframe   allowfullscreen></iframe><br />
Known for their breakout hit BROFORCE, the SA collective known as Free Lives decided to run a game jam on a remote island. It's kind of like survivor but with game developers and no one actually gets voted off. Frog Smashers is the only game to come out of Game Jam Island. It tells the tale of a simple misunderstanding at a bus stop that leads to the end of frogkind.</p>
<p>We’ll be showcasing all these games and more Thursday, September 6th, at 7:00PM at North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702, with a short introduction at 8:00PM. The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!</p>]]></content><author><name>{&quot;login&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;&quot;juegosrancheros@gmail.com&quot;, &quot;display_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;first_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS&quot;, &quot;last_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;RANCHEROS&quot;}</name><email>juegosrancheros@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Events" /><category term="juegosrancheros" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[JUEGOS RANCHEROS is excited to share DEEP SOUTH AFRICA, a trio of games from developers based in South Africa. Join us this Thursday, Sept 6th, at 7:00PM at Austin’s North Door for a look at Semblance, Helping Hand, and Frog Smashers. [RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK BY CLICKING HERE!] Created by duo Nyamakop, Semblance is described as a "true platformer". What does that even mean? Well you can literally manipulate platforms with your body in this soft and squishy world. Come check out one of the first games from South Africa to be released on the Switch. Every play a dialogue driven narrative game, but only wanted to respond to every character by giving them the finger? Well in Helping Hand you can! Along with a variety of different hand gestures you can navigate this Adult Swim show-esque game with just the use of 5 fingers. Known for their breakout hit BROFORCE, the SA collective known as Free Lives decided to run a game jam on a remote island. It's kind of like survivor but with game developers and no one actually gets voted off. Frog Smashers is the only game to come out of Game Jam Island. It tells the tale of a simple misunderstanding at a bus stop that leads to the end of frogkind. We’ll be showcasing all these games and more Thursday, September 6th, at 7:00PM at North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702, with a short introduction at 8:00PM. The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">JUEGOS RANCHEROS PRESENTS: HOT LOCAL FLAVORS</title><link href="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/08/01/juegos-rancheros-presents-hot-local-flavors.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="JUEGOS RANCHEROS PRESENTS: HOT LOCAL FLAVORS" /><published>2018-08-01T15:09:31-05:00</published><updated>2018-08-01T15:09:31-05:00</updated><id>https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/08/01/juegos-rancheros-presents-hot-local-flavors</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://gamesyall.com/events/2018/08/01/juegos-rancheros-presents-hot-local-flavors.html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-2175" src="/images/jr-archive/lead_image_august_1280-300x162.png" alt=""   /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>JUEGOS RANCHEROS is excited to share HOT LOCAL FLAVORS, a collection of upcoming and recently released games created in and around our very own Austin, Texas. Join us this <span class="aBn" tabindex="0" data-term="goog_124140652"><span class="aQJ">Thursday, August 2nd, at 7:00PM</span></span> at Austin’s North Door for a look at <em>Red Star Azimuth</em>, <em>The Indie Game Legend 3D</em>, <em>Imperishable Memories</em>, and more!</p>
<p>[ <a href="https://www.facebook.com/events/208878693124142/">RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK BY CLICKING HERE!</a> ]</p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/iuRn64GqOC4"  ></iframe></p>
<p>We’re mesmerized by the visual landscape in <a href="http://teamdogpit.com/redstarazimuth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=http://teamdogpit.com/redstarazimuth/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1533240414069000&amp;usg=AFQjCNFMgbDCKXLe9COfaGc2vmJ5Of2ReQ">Red Star Azimuth</a>. Manuela Malasaña is creating a first person hacking puzzle game with am 80’s vaporwave aesthetic. Manuela has been posting some <a href="https://twitter.com/ManuelaXibanya/status/1021200159978459137" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=https://twitter.com/ManuelaXibanya/status/1021200159978459137&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1533240414069000&amp;usg=AFQjCNFuLfWscdcqmEHuGHp9ckzckqXyDA">stunning images</a> on her twitter feed. Come see why we’re hyped at getting a first look of the memory prism inside of “Vaporland”.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/VlGIQqdQepA"  ></iframe></p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VlGIQqdQepA" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3DVlGIQqdQepA&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1533240414069000&amp;usg=AFQjCNH1sHemwuTn_FD95nQUGWEV2CLTGg">https://www.youtube.com/watch?<wbr />v=VlGIQqdQepA</a></p>
<p>Continuing in first person perspectives, we’re excited to show Jeff Lindsay’s <a href="http://indiegamelegend.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=http://indiegamelegend.com/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1533240414069000&amp;usg=AFQjCNHv-m_ji3B6f5NoLmHPvQFHYvFpaw">The Indie Game Legend 3D</a>. A cult-classic dungeon shoot em ‘up created during the early days of the <a href="https://forums.tigsource.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=https://forums.tigsource.com/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1533240414069000&amp;usg=AFQjCNFPBb2C08grIVHltBhPgYtwApYqqA">TIGSource forum</a> is reimagined and expanded as a first-person shooter-vania. Come learn the history and explore the future of this underground labyrinth. Try to rescue captured indie game creators in this quirky underground adventure.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-2181" src="/images/jr-archive/imperishable_memories_2-300x169.gif" alt=""   /></p>
<p>Previous Juegos Rancheros <a href="http://juegosrancheros.com/1752/events/boa-retina/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=http://juegosrancheros.com/1752/events/boa-retina/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1533240414069000&amp;usg=AFQjCNEAibv1h_kDyjMnXVop5LLULWJlng">artist resident</a> Jennifer Raye returns! We’re excited to show the near-final release of her <a href="https://jenniferraye.itch.io/imperishable-memories" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=https://jenniferraye.itch.io/imperishable-memories&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1533240414069000&amp;usg=AFQjCNEhAfhUPz5lH7KTq0kIJpkf7nSpMQ">Imperishable Memories</a>. Journey through this narrative shoot ‘em up and explore unforgotten emotions and experiences. Can you grab a hold of the past…or perhaps enemies on your way?</p>
<p>All of these local developers will be here to show off their latest creations. Come say hi!</p>
<p>We’ll be showcasing all these games and more <span class="aBn" tabindex="0" data-term="goog_124140653"><span class="aQJ">Thursday, August 2nd, at 7:00PM</span></span> at North Door, <a href="https://maps.google.com/?q=501+Brushy+Street,+Austin,+TX+78702&amp;entry=gmail&amp;source=g">501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702</a>, with a short introduction at <span class="aBn" tabindex="0" data-term="goog_124140654"><span class="aQJ">8:00PM.</span></span> The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!</p>]]></content><author><name>{&quot;login&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;&quot;juegosrancheros@gmail.com&quot;, &quot;display_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;first_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS&quot;, &quot;last_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;RANCHEROS&quot;}</name><email>juegosrancheros@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Events" /><category term="juegosrancheros" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[&nbsp; JUEGOS RANCHEROS is excited to share HOT LOCAL FLAVORS, a collection of upcoming and recently released games created in and around our very own Austin, Texas. Join us this Thursday, August 2nd, at 7:00PM at Austin’s North Door for a look at Red Star Azimuth, The Indie Game Legend 3D, Imperishable Memories, and more! [ RSVP FOR THIS EVENT AND INVITE YOUR FRIENDS ON FACEBOOK BY CLICKING HERE! ] We’re mesmerized by the visual landscape in Red Star Azimuth. Manuela Malasaña is creating a first person hacking puzzle game with am 80’s vaporwave aesthetic. Manuela has been posting some stunning images on her twitter feed. Come see why we’re hyped at getting a first look of the memory prism inside of “Vaporland”. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VlGIQqdQepA Continuing in first person perspectives, we’re excited to show Jeff Lindsay’s The Indie Game Legend 3D. A cult-classic dungeon shoot em ‘up created during the early days of the TIGSource forum is reimagined and expanded as a first-person shooter-vania. Come learn the history and explore the future of this underground labyrinth. Try to rescue captured indie game creators in this quirky underground adventure. Previous Juegos Rancheros artist resident Jennifer Raye returns! We’re excited to show the near-final release of her Imperishable Memories. Journey through this narrative shoot ‘em up and explore unforgotten emotions and experiences. Can you grab a hold of the past…or perhaps enemies on your way? All of these local developers will be here to show off their latest creations. Come say hi! We’ll be showcasing all these games and more Thursday, August 2nd, at 7:00PM at North Door, 501 Brushy Street, Austin, TX 78702, with a short introduction at 8:00PM. The show is free, all ages, and open to all the public, so come join us as we drink, play and meet the people changing the way we think about games!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome our new board members!</title><link href="https://gamesyall.com/news/2018/07/30/welcome-our-new-board-members.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome our new board members!" /><published>2018-07-30T23:03:24-05:00</published><updated>2018-07-30T23:03:24-05:00</updated><id>https://gamesyall.com/news/2018/07/30/welcome-our-new-board-members</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://gamesyall.com/news/2018/07/30/welcome-our-new-board-members.html"><![CDATA[<p>Juegos Rancheros put out a call for new leadership and we're happy to say some real fine folks stepped up to help! These new board members will help with bringing you new monthly events to celebrate indie games in Austin, managing the annual Fantastic Arcade festival, and collaborating with the Museum of Human Achievement on artists residencies for the Arcade of Anything gallery space.</p>
<p>Without further ado, we proudly introduce the newest additions to the Juegos Rancheros Board of Directors— Saam Pahlavan, Rusty Moyher, and Autumn Taylor. Here’s a little more information about each one of our new board members:</p>
<p><img class="size-medium wp-image-2155 alignright" src="/images/jr-archive/me_portrait-300x212.jpg" alt=""  >Taco Illuminat</span></a>i based out of Austin, TX .</span></p>
<p class="gmail-p1"><span class="gmail-s1">His passion for videogames extends into a long series of <a href="https://twitter.com/saampahlavan/status/773384024958042112"><span class="gmail-s3">excellent game ideas</span></a> , <a href="http://loadingscreenpodcast.com/"><span class="gmail-s3">interviewing fellow developers</span></a>, and being a <a href="https://www.austinchronicle.com/daily/screens/2013-09-20/takeaways-from-fantastic-arcade-day-1/"><span class="gmail-s3">local folk hero</span></a>.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img class="size-medium wp-image-2154 alignleft" src="/images/jr-archive/headshot-A-512-300x300.png" alt=""   /></p>
<p class="gmail-p1"><span class="gmail-s3"><a href="http://twitter.com/rustym">Rusty Moyher</a></span><span class="gmail-s1"> is the independent videogame creator who <a href="http://rustymoyher.com/"><span class="gmail-s3">builds and publishes work</span></a> under the moniker Wild Rooster.</span></p>
<p class="gmail-p1"><span class="gmail-s1">With a passion for bringing people together, his projects often focus on local multiplayer experiences including his long-running <a href="http://rustymoyher.com/astroduel"><span class="gmail-s3">Astro Duel</span></a> series and the critically-acclaimed party game <a href="http://rustymoyher.com/bloop"><span class="gmail-s3">BLOOP</span></a>  He also co-created, kickstarted and released the seven-part <a href="http://retrogamecrunch.com/"><span class="gmail-s3">Retro Game Crunch</span></a> collection and runs the nightly tournaments at <a href="http://fantasticarcade.com/"><span class="gmail-s3">Fantastic Arcade</span></a>.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img class="size-medium wp-image-2153 alignright" src="/images/jr-archive/AutumnTaylor_VRheadshot-300x300.jpg" alt=""   /></p>
<p class="gmail-p1"><span class="gmail-s3"><a href="https://twitter.com/lusterly_">Autumn Rose Taylor</a></span><span class="gmail-s1"> is a community organizer and business/communications professional that lives and breathes virtual reality. </span></p>
<p class="gmail-p1"><span class="gmail-s1">In addition to her community efforts with JUEGOS RANCHEROS, Taylor co-organizes <a href="https://vraustin.org/"><span class="gmail-s3">VR Austin</span></a>, the annual <a href="https://vraustin.org/vrjam/"><span class="gmail-s3">VR Austin Jam</span></a>, and focuses her community work on diversity and advocating for women/non-binary individuals in the video game and virtual reality industries at large. She is currently Studio Director at <a href="https://owlchemylabs.com/"><span class="gmail-s3">Owlchemy Labs</span></a>. </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="gmail-p1"><span class="gmail-s1">These good people applied to board membership during our recent call for new members. That application is now closed, but we are looking for help with committees working on Fantastic Arcade around the corner on October 25-28, as well as our local monthly events highlighting the best in indie games from around the world and in our own backyard. To find out more information about about getting involved in these committees, email <span class="gmail-s3"><a href="mailto:juegosrancheros@gmail.org">juegosrancheros@gmail.com</a>.</span></span></p>
<p class="gmail-p1"><span class="gmail-s1">We are excited for the contributions of our new board members and future contributions of committee members to the Juegos Rancheros organization, the indie games community in Austin, and beyond.</span></p>]]></content><author><name>{&quot;login&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;&quot;juegosrancheros@gmail.com&quot;, &quot;display_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS RANCHEROS&quot;, &quot;first_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;JUEGOS&quot;, &quot;last_name&quot;=&gt;&quot;RANCHEROS&quot;}</name><email>juegosrancheros@gmail.com</email></author><category term="News" /><category term="juegosrancheros" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juegos Rancheros put out a call for new leadership and we're happy to say some real fine folks stepped up to help! These new board members will help with bringing you new monthly events to celebrate indie games in Austin, managing the annual Fantastic Arcade festival, and collaborating with the Museum of Human Achievement on artists residencies for the Arcade of Anything gallery space. Without further ado, we proudly introduce the newest additions to the Juegos Rancheros Board of Directors— Saam Pahlavan, Rusty Moyher, and Autumn Taylor. Here’s a little more information about each one of our new board members: Taco Illuminati based out of Austin, TX . His passion for videogames extends into a long series of excellent game ideas , interviewing fellow developers, and being a local folk hero. &nbsp; Rusty Moyher is the independent videogame creator who builds and publishes work under the moniker Wild Rooster. With a passion for bringing people together, his projects often focus on local multiplayer experiences including his long-running Astro Duel series and the critically-acclaimed party game BLOOP  He also co-created, kickstarted and released the seven-part Retro Game Crunch collection and runs the nightly tournaments at Fantastic Arcade. &nbsp; &nbsp; Autumn Rose Taylor is a community organizer and business/communications professional that lives and breathes virtual reality.  In addition to her community efforts with JUEGOS RANCHEROS, Taylor co-organizes VR Austin, the annual VR Austin Jam, and focuses her community work on diversity and advocating for women/non-binary individuals in the video game and virtual reality industries at large. She is currently Studio Director at Owlchemy Labs.  &nbsp; These good people applied to board membership during our recent call for new members. That application is now closed, but we are looking for help with committees working on Fantastic Arcade around the corner on October 25-28, as well as our local monthly events highlighting the best in indie games from around the world and in our own backyard. To find out more information about about getting involved in these committees, email juegosrancheros@gmail.com. We are excited for the contributions of our new board members and future contributions of committee members to the Juegos Rancheros organization, the indie games community in Austin, and beyond.]]></summary></entry></feed>